
Known issues:
------------

	PEEL:
		- phantom support is busted.
		- can't disable more than 12 engines (since keyboards only have F1 -> F12 keys).
		- some convex objects are not rendered when the ICE convex hull code fails.
		- some "add objects" tests include in their timings the cost of creating render objects. That's not good.
		And sometimes it also includes the cost of the PEEL plugins trying to share shapes, rather than the cost
		of the physics engine itself. This part needs some more work.
		- stats seem wrong in fracture scene.
		- the configurable tests & "presets" limit what the script can run, as opposed to PEEL 1.0.

	Stats plugin:
		- stats are not updated when an object is deleted.
	
	Bullet:
		- the local inertia is apparently not correctly set (or not correcty computed) for capsules and
		convexes. PhysX / Havok / Newton all return similar values for this, but Bullet's values are higher
		for some reason (i.e. the values returned by Pint::GetLocalInertia()).
		- same for compounds
		- ragdoll's joints are not properly setup. It works in other engines, no idea what I'm doing wrong.
		- capsule's local rot does not work in CreateScene_Capsule2SlidingOnCurvedMesh.

	Havok:
		- triangles are not backface culled in raytracing tests, producing slightly unfair comparisons.
		How do we enable backface culling there?
		- memory usage might be incorrectly captured. Not entirely sure what's the proper way.
		- Voronoi fracture scene acts very strangely in newer Havok versions, although the same scene & setup code
		works fine in older versions.
		- some kinematic scenes are crashing with old versions of Havok.
		- capsule's local rot does not work in CreateScene_Capsule2SlidingOnCurvedMesh.
		- articulations only support spherical joints without limits. Good for ropes, not for vehicles.
		- support for articulations is fragile and limited at the moment, which makes only basic scenes work
		and other ones crash. Articulations are currently disabled to avoid these.
		- mass properties of compound objects are not properly computed.
		
	Newton:
		- ragdoll/ragdoll collision filtering does not work.
		- deleting an object is not implemented, so the Voronoi fracture scene isn't properly setup.
		- friction/restitution values are not properly passed to Newton.
		- prismatic joint limits not the same as PhysX. Needs a remapping.
		- for some reason the Newton 3.12 / 3.13 / 3.14 PINT plugins do not build in Debug at the moment.
		- it seems that the sleeping problem is back in 3.14 (cannot really be disabled anymore).
		- 3.14 crashes in some tests that were previously working. It is kind of expected since that one
		was built from the Newton trunk, not from a stable release.

	PhysX:
		- the PhysX 3.3.3 PINT plugin is missing. Not sure it's worth adding.
		- distance joints not working well in 2.8.4 (maybe not properly setup).
		- distance joints not working well in NovodeX (maybe not properly setup).
		- the PhysX 3.4 GPU pipeline does not support articulations. Scenes with articulations will not
		be created properly.
		- the PhysX 3.4 GPU pipeline is still a work in progress. It has some known issues regarding for
		example mesh collisions against internal edges, etc. It is known that the GPU version will have
		more simulation artefacts as the CPU version. This should get ironed out in the future.

TODO:
----

	PEEL:
		- revisit "add objects" scenes. Ideally we'd rely on the plugins themselves to record & report the time spent
		in the physics engine. Or we need specialized virtual calls to do "batch adds" at runtime, while all the
		necessary data has been computed before (not timed).
		- the 'SQ Profiling Mode' stuff is confusing. It would be better to replace the 'ProfileUpdate' function with
		just something defining the preferred profiling mode for each test, while still leaving the option to override
		this with the UI parameter.
		- better test scenes for actors insertion, e.g. 10000 adds while the scene already has 30K objects.
		- add proper "mesh cooking" benchmarks.
		- add more convex sweeps scenes.
		- add support for heightfields (all engines).
		- add support for character controllers.
		- add better support for vehicles.
		- share rendering objects between engines. This is done in very few tests, but it should be done everywhere.

	Bullet:
		- support kinematics.
		- support overlaps.
		- support multithreading.
		- support 'raycast any' and 'raycast all'.
		- support prismatic joint limits.
		- support mCOMLocalOffset (what I tried didn't work).
		- support "aggregates" if available.
		- support "articulations" if available.

	Havok:
		- use 'combineMassProperties' for compounds.
		- support box overlaps.
		- support capsule overlaps.
		- support 'raycast any' and 'raycast all'.
		- support prismatic joint limits.
		- support "aggregates" if available.
		- better support for "articulations".

	Newton:
		- complete PINT plugin (sweeps, overlaps, raycast any, CCD, disable sleeping, etc, etc).
		- support "aggregates" if available.
		- support "articulations" if available.

	PhysX:
		- support for convex sweeps is not implemented for all versions. Complete this.
		- support prismatic joint limits (2.8.4 and Novodex).
		- support mCOMLocalOffset in all PhysX plugins (currently supported by all plugins >= 3.2).

	All engines:
		- there's a lot of common code to refactor in all the different PINT plugins.
